Guide to the James Paddock Collman Papers SC1138
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Trips
  - NAS Regional Roundtable, UCSF, 1987 Jan 12 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Electrochemical Society meeting, Honolulu, 1987 Oct 18-23 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Canoe trip to Minnesota, 1987 Aug 4-18 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Symposium on Macrocyclic Chemistry, Florence, Italy. NO GO., 1986 Sep 1-4 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - XXIV Intl Conf on Coord Chem, Athens, Greece. NO GO., 1986 Aug 24-29 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - ACS meeting, Cope Symposium, 1986 fall (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - ACS meeting, NY, NY, 1986 Apr (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - DuPont, MIT, 1986 Apr (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - NAS Regional Roundtable, San Francisco, 1986 Jan 31 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - France, 1986 May 20-Jun 25 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - EUCHEM Conf Molecular Materials for Electronics and Opto-Electronics, Les Arcs, 1986 Jan 13-17 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - ONR Contractor's meeting, Elkridge, 1985 Jan 6-9 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Workshop on Conductive Polymers, Brookhaven, 1985 Oct 6-9 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Lincoln, Nebraska, 1985 Dec 10-13 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - New Zealand/Australia trip, 1985 Mar (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Pacifichem 95 Hawaii, 1995 Dec 17-22 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - John C. Bailar Jr. Lecturer, Urbana IL, 1995 Aug (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - 210th ACS National Meeting, Chicago, IL, 1995 Aug 20-25 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - EAC Annual Meeting, 1995 May 3-5 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Seminar, UT El Paso, 1995 Apr 13 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - National Academy of Sciences 132 annual meeting (D.C.), 1995 Apr 22-25 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - New Mexico, 1995 Apr 14 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - ACS Mtg. Anaheim, CA, 1995 Apr 2-6 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Henry Taube Symposium, 1995 Mar 30-31 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Europe, 1995 May (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Itinerary for Prof. & Mrs. James P. Collman, 1995 May 16-29 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - NAS Annual Meeting, 1994 Apr 24-26 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - UNC Chapel Hill, 1994 Mar 18-19 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - CIT, 1994 Mar 2-3 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Europe-France, 1994 Apr 11-20 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Prof. Warren Roper, New Zealand, 1994 Nov 7 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - LAS Alumni Achievement Award, 1994 Sep 30-Oct 2 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Iowa State University of Science, 1994 Sep 8-9 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - 9th Int'l Symposium on Homo. Catalysis, Israel, 1994 Aug 21-26 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Gordon Research Conferences, 1994 Jul 24-29 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - France, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Royal Netherlands Chemical Society, 1994 Apr 21-22 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Beckman Institute External Advisory Comm, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Hoechst Celanese Corporation, 1994 May 27 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Ida Beam Lectures-U of Iowa, 1994 Apr 27-29 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Dr. Penny Brothers-Univ. of Auckland, NZ, 1993 Dec 7 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - U of Illinois-Beckman Institute Advisory Comm., 1993 May 26-28 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Scripps Res. Inst. "Frontiers...", 1993 Feb 19 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - National Academy of Sciences Meeting, SF, CA, 1993 Feb 22 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Yale, 1993 Mar 23 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Dupont, 1993 Mar 24-25 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - ACS Meeting-Denver, 1993 Mar 28-Apr 2 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Florida Catalysis conf., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Florida Catalysis conf., 1993 Apr 19-23 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Visitor - Eiichi kimura, Hiroshima, Japan, 1993 Apr 25-26 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Europe - France, 1993 May 10-18 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Bell Laboratories, 1993 May 3 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - NAS Meeting, 1993 Apr 25-27 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - University of Texas, 1963 Apr 29-30 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Metallo-Mesogens--Spain, 1993 Jun 3-5 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - 6th Int'l Conf. Bioinorganic chemistry, 1993 Aug 23-27 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Stiefvater, Charles A. Lecture. Univ. of Nebraska., 1992 Sep 3-6 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Stille Science Symposium - Colorado, 1992 May 30 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Pohang Inst. of Sci. and Tech., Korea, 1992 May 16-May 18 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Industrial Affiliates Program Collman 60th Birthday, 1992 Apr 4 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - ARCO/Univ. of Pennsylvania, 1993 Mar 21-22 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - SF ACS Symposium, 1992 Apr 4-10 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - University of Virginia-Pratt Lec., 1992 Apr (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Harvard MIT Inorganic Lecture Series, 1992 Apr 20-21 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - National Academy of Sciences-Washington, 1992 Apr 26-29 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Lecture at Columbia Univ., 1992 Mar 5 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Harvey Mudd Lecture, 1991 Oct 17-18 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Stanford Centennial Celebration, 1991 Sep 28-Oct 2 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Fischer Symp. Karlsruhe, FRG, 1991 Jun 16-20 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - EUCHEM Conference-Bavaria, 1991 Sep 15-20 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - JPC Vacation, 1991 Jul 24-Aug 8 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Kyoto Japan-Toshiba Intl School of SuperCond., 1991 Jul (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Oklahama State University, 1991 Apr 25-26 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - ACS Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1991 Apr (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Davis Lecture, U. New Orleans, 1991 Mar (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Santa Barbara Trip, 1991 Mar 7-8 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - NAS Regional Meeting, 1991 Jan 31 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - ACS Meeting, SF, 1990 Oct 31-Nov 2 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Univ. of Oregon, 1990 Oct 25-28 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Pauling Symposium, U. Washington, 1990 Oct 6 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Fort Collins/Yellowstone trip, 1990 Sep 7-13 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - High School Reunion, 1990 Jun 30-Jul 1 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Little Conference, Sierra Camp Lodge, S. Lake Tahoe, 1990 May 20-24 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Gettysburg College Musselman Lect., 1990 Apr 19-20 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Washington ACS Meeting/Murray Roast, 1990 Aug 25-Sep 2 (Box 12, Folder 92)
- Research Reports
  - Arnold, Hilary, 1990 Jul 10 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Baran, Alexandra (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Barnes, Craig (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bartmann, Ekkehard (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Brothers, Penelope: Heterolytic Activation of Hydrogen by Transition Metal Complexes. (review) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bencosme, Susana (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bressan, Mario (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Brothers, Penelope: Heterolytic Activation of Hydrogen by Transition Metal Complexes. (review) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Cahen, David (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Cawse, James N. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Chong, Tony (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Christian, Paul (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Clark, Dennis (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Collins, Terry (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Cooke, Manning (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Davis, Dennis (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Davis, Duane (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Denisevich, Peter (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Dolcetti, Guiliano (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Doxsee, Kenneth (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Erk, Peter, 1990 Jul (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Erk, Peter, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Evitt, Eric R. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Evitt, Eric (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Finke, Richard (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Finn, M.G. (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Finn, M.G., 1988 Jul (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Fitzgerald, Jeffrey (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Fitzgerald, Jeffrey (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Fitzgerald, Jeffrey, 1986 Jul (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Gagne, Robert (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Garner, Mike (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Groh, Susan (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Grubbs, Robert H. (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Ha, Yunkyoung. Research report, 1988 Dec (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Halbert, Tom (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Hampton, Philip, 1986 Sep (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Hampton, Philip, 1987 Jul (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hayes, Susan (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hayashi, Teruyuki (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hegedus, Louis S. research report (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Heitner, Howard (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hendricks, Neil (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hendricks, Neil H. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Inventory of fuel-cell related prophyrins - Neil Hendricks, 1985 Oct 28 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Hercules research reports. Hercules, Inc. Research Center., 1969 Apr - 1972 Apr (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Hoffman, Norris W. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hopkins, Ted (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Horn, Raymond W. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Hosking, John (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hoyano, James K. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hutchison, James. Research report, 1987 Dec (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Kevin E. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Kahrl, James (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Kellen-Yuen, Cynthia. Research report., 1991 May 21 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Kim, Kimoon (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Kodadek, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Kodadek, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Komoto, Robert (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Konai, Yutaka (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Kosydar, Karen (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Transmetallation - K. Kosydar (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Kouba, Jay (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Kreh, Robert P. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Kronstadt, Michael (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Kuroda, Yasuhisa (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Kuznetsov, Boris (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Lamanna, William (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Lapporte, Sy (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Ledon, Henry (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Lee, Virgil. Progress report., 1989 Jan 24 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Lee, Virgil, 1988 Jul (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lee, Virgil. Research report., 1990 Apr 2 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - L'Her, Maurice (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - L'Her, Maurice report, 1980 Oct (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - L'Her, Maurice. Research report (original), 1980 Sep (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - L'Her, Maurice, 1986 May (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - L'Her research report: Electrocatalysis of O2 reduction (xerox copy) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - L'Her, Maurice. research report, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - L'Her, Maurice (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Libit, Lawrence (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Lin, Doris (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Lopez, Michel-Angel. Synthesis Protocol. (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Lotz, Tobias J. (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - MacLaury, Michael (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - U.S. - U.S.S.R. Cooperation in Catalysis - Research Report. M. MacLaury (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Madonik, Alex (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Marchon, Jean-Claude (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Marquardt, Don (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Marrocco, Mathew (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Miller, Bryan D. (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Matlock, Paul (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - McAllister, Craig (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - McDevitt, John T., 1983 Oct-nov (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - McMahon, Michele, 1989 Jun (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Meier, Kurt (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Milan, David (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Milan, David, 1989 spring (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Moelwyn-Hughes, Tim (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Moelwyn-Hughes, Tim. Laboratory Notebook, 1970 Feb 10 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Moriarity, John L. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Morris, Donald. Research reports #1 and 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Morris, Donald E. Summary of literature on transition metal cluster compounds (through May 1968), 1968 May (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Murphy, Don (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Nelson, Norvell (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Neuberg, Kim (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Norton, Jack (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Oakley, Richard (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Ozawa, Toshihiko (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Pettman, Roger (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Prodolliet, Jacques (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Raybuck, Scott (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Rose, Eric. Research report., 1985 Sep (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Rothrock, Richard (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Roustan, Jean-Louis (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - San Filippo, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Schmidkonz, Bertram. Research report., 1988 Mar (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Schmidkonz, Bertram., 1988 Apr (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Schmittou, Eric (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Sessler, Jon (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Sessler, Jon (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Shapley, John R. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Siegl, Walter (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Sharpless, Barry (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Sklar, Larry (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Slagen, Peter. Paper (background) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Sorrell, Tom (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Stark, Rex (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Suslick, Ken (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Takaya, Hidemasa (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Takaya, Hidemasa, and Winkler, Barbara (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Takeda, Makoto (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Tanaka, Hiroo. Research reports, 5/89-11/89, 1989 May-Nov (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Tanaka, Hiroo. Research report., 1989 Apr (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tanaka, Hiroo. Research report., 1988 Dec (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tanaka, Hiroo, 1988 June (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Tanaka, Hiroo, 1987 Oct (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Takimoto, Chris (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Tovrog, Ben (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Tustin, Gerald (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Valentine, Don, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Valentine, Don (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Valentine, Joan (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Valentine, Joan. Research report. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Venburg, Gregory (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Wahren, Robert (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Wahren, Helena (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Wann, Grady (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Winkler, Barbara (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Winker, Tammo (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Winter, Stan (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Woo, L. Keith (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Wright, James. Group seminar, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Wright, James (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Zisk, Matthew, 1990 Aug 28 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Zisk, Matthew B., 1989 Aug (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Slides
  - Slides -- Homogeneous Catalysis (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Slides -- Figures, originals, manuscripts to be published (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 1969 summer (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Slide drawings, 1970 Jun (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Slides for lectures, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Slides for SUNY, Buffalo & I.C.C.C., 1972 Jun (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Slides (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 1970 Dec (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Patent Related
  - NSF GP20273X - Invention Sel. Syntheses of Aliphatic Ketones JPC, S. Winter, 1972 Mar (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Patent application -- Synthesis of Alkali Metal ... and Method of Producing Alkali Metal ... NSF, 1973 Jun (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NSF GP20273X Invention Disclosure Selective Syntheses of Carboxylic Acids & Carboxylic Acid ..., 1972 Sep (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Patent application -- Synthesis of Hemifluorinated Ketones, 1973 Mar (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Writings
  - Prep of Sodium Tetracarbonylferrate(-II), JPC and S. Winter (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Prep of Na2Fe(CO)4 Dioxane in 1,4 Dioxane (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Alfa brochure -- Disodium Iron Tetracarbonyl Reagent (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Group reports, etc. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Reprints authored or co-authored by James Paddock Collman (Box 13-18)
- Chrono Files
  - 1990 (Box 9)
  - 1990 Sep-1990 Dec (Box 10)
  - A-L, 1991 Jan 1-1991 Dec 31 (Box 10)
  - M-Z, 1991 Jan 1-1991 Dec 31 (Box 9)
  - A-L, 1992 Jan 1-1992 Dec 31 (Box 9)
  - M-Z, 1992 Jan 1-1992 Dec 31 (Box 9)
  - 1993 (Box 10)
- Data
  - SIMS Data (Box 19, Folder 1-14)
- Additional materials, ARCH-2016-067
  - 213th American Chemical Society National Meeting: James P. Collman, Alfred Bader Award in Bioinorganic or Bioorganic Chemistry, 1997-4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Introduction to Organic Chemistry, Chemistry 33, 1996/1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Introduction to Organic Chemistry: A different perspective on key concepts, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry 32: The Frontiers of Chemical Science, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Introduction to Organic Chemistry: Chemistry 33, 1989/1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)